

I'm a **Web Developer** with a focus on **Frontend**. I have experience in HTML/CSS layout and Quality Assurance Testing.

I'm also a **Graphic Designer** with an emphasis on **Animation** and I have extensive experience since 2011.

I have skills in planning, innovation, creativity, negotiation, teamwork, results orientation, problem solving and Agile project management with SCRUM.

EXPERIENCE

QA Feb. 2023 - Oct.2023

- · Test of the bots developed by Cari AI
- · Test implementations from the Dashboard of bots, such as: (NLP) Machine Learning, Crud API, CRM, intelligent document processing (IDP).
- · Design and execution of test cases
- · API testing
- · Static and dynamic tests

PLACE: Defytek.

SKILLS: SCRUM, Testing, API Rest, Postman.

Graphic designer

Sep. 2020 - Jul. 2021

- · Graphic design pieces for Enel X's social networks Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn.
- · Graphic and web design of emails for Enel X and Enel.
- · Creation of videos and animations for Enel X social networks.
- · Design of the Enel X campaigns proposed by the team.

PLACE: Datagran

SKILLS: Lean, Animation, HTML, CSS.

Graphic creative

9 months 2019 - 2020

Responsible for the creation of the following pieces for Rappi:

- · Design for publications on social networks.
- · Design in the Look & Feel updates of the App.
- · Graphic design with implementation of gifs for email marketing.
- · Introduction of the products of the associated SMEs to the brand in the promotions of its restaurants.

PLACE: Wavemaker

SKILLS: Agile, Animation, HTML, CSS.

Teaching - full time

6 months - 2018

- · Responsible and advisor of the 4th and 7th semester groups in the execution of their integrative projects.
- · Tutorials and academic projects as substantive work.
- · Full-time teacher with the following subjects:
- Digital retouching.
- Animation and editing.
- Photo-design.
- Editorial illustration.
- Audiovisual communication.
- Fundamentals of photography.
- History of Colombian art.
- Brand and branding development.

PLACE: Corporación Unificada Nacional CUN. Graphic Design program. Tolima Regional.

SKILLS: Effective communication, leadership, empathy.

EDUCATION

Cetified Tech Developer Emphasis in Frontend

Digital House (Argentina)

Intermediate English B1-B2 2017- Present

U. Distrital Language Institute and Duolingo

Professional Graphic Design 2017 Emphasis in Animation

2021-2023

Escuela de Artes y Letras

Diploma in animation 2016

AniMadeLab - U. Nacional - Colciencias

Advanced digital retouching 2015

Zona cinco - Film and Photography School

Digital illustration 2014

Zona cinco - Film and Photography School

SKILLS

Figma

Javascript

React

Git

Shell

MySQL

Java

Postman

Adobe Creative Cloud

Blender



+57 318 481 2572



/DaisyDewD



d.dew.design@gmail.com



@daisy.dew.art





portfolio-daisydew.vercel.app